Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series I. 1963-1965
  - Cornell University Libraries, Olin and Mann. McCarthy, Stephen A.; Healey, George H. Lafayette Book Collection., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Archives and Regional History., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Fox, Edith M.
  - Festival of Contemporary Arts., 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Panofsky, Erwin.
  - WHCU. Hanna, Michael R., 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Photographic Science., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Dameron, Maclean.
  - Willard Straight Hall., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Personnel Office., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Willers, Diedrich K.
  - University Placement Office., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Stutz, Frederick H.
  - Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Garson, Inez; Seley, Jason; Squier, Jack L.
  - Big Red Barn., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Ball, William H.
  - Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid., 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Corson, Dale R.; Anderson, Jon T. Student Employment Committee; Financial aid.
  - University Relations., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Holley, Robert W.; Marcham, John; Kidera, Robert A.; Grohmann, H. Victor; Sartre, Jean-Paul. Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art; Sartre visit publicity.
  - University Faculty., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Meetings, Agenda., 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Murphy, Royse P.
  - University Faculty Minutes., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 44-46)
  - Dean of the Faculty., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Murphy, Royse P. Undergraduate education.
  - Dean of the Faculty., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Murphy, Royse P.; Mackesey, Thomas W. Reorganization of the University Faculty.
  - Faculty Committees., 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Council., 1958-1964 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Military Science and Physical Training., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - University Lectures., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Prizes., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Student Conduct., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    Marcham, John.
  - Calendar., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Music., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Economic Status of the Faculty., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Necrology., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Academic Freedom and Tenure., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Dean, William Tucker; Clark, M. Garner.
  - Pensions and Retirement., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - New Faculty List., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Salaries of Faculty and Assistants., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Palm, Charles E.; Raffensperger, Edgar M. Extension Service; American Council on Education.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Palm, Charles E.; Harrar, George. Rockefeller Foundation; Committee to Plan a Study of the Future Role of the College of Agriculture.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Departments., 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Malott, Deane W. Botany Dept.; Animal experimentation.
  - Cornell University Laboratory of Ornithology., 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Pettingill, Olin Sewall; Alien, Arthur A.; Stuart, Lyman K.
  - Bailey Hortorium., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Lawrence, George H.M.
  - Biology., 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Boynton, Damon; Srb, Adrian M.; Galston, Arthur W.; Wallace, Bruce. Division of Biological Sciences.
  - Extension Service., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Johnson, Alvin A.; Harrington, Clifford R.
  - College of Architecture., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Kelly, Burnham. Richard King Mellon Charitable Trusts.
  - College of Architecture., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Parsons, Kermit C.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Brown, Stuart M.; Skinner, G. William. Ford Foundation; Society for the Humanities; Six Year Ph.D. Program.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Ford Foundation; College of Arts and Sciences Humanities Council.
  - Dept. of Economics., 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Golay, Frank H.; Hildebrand, George H.
  - Dept. of Chemistry., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Miller, William T.
  - Far Eastern Studies., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Kahin, George McT.; Golay, Frank H. Southeast Asia Program.
  - Computing Center., 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Lesser, Richard C.
  - Music Dept., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Laube, Vivian F.; Campbell, William A.
  - Band., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Campbell, William A.
  - Sage Chapel Choir., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Sokol, Thomas A.; Grover, John E.
  - Departments., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Kahin, George McT.; Lewis, John W.; Gold, Thomas; Sola, Donald F.; Rabinowitz, Isaac; Stycos, Joseph Mayone.
  - Romance Literature., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Dieckmann, Herbert; Demorest, Jean-Jacques.
  - Psychology., 1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Physics., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Parratt, Lyman G.
  - Sociology and Anthropology. Streib, Gordon F., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Center for International Studies., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Kahin, George McT.; Mints, I.I.; Sisakian, N.M.; Muller, Steven. Ford Foundation; USSR Academy of Sciences.
  - Center for International Studies. Muller, Steven. Institute for Policy Studies., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Center for International Studies., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Muller, Steven; Sisakian, N.M.; Mints, I.I. Ford Foundation.
  - Center for International Studies., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Muller, Steven; Squier, Jack L. Ford Foundation; Cornell Latin American Program.
  - Center for International Studies., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Muller, Steven. Ford Foundation.
  - School of Civil Engineering., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Christensen, N.A. Graduate School admissions.
  - College of Engineering., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Schultz, Andrew. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; Materials Science Center.
  - College of Engineering. Berth, Donald F.; Corson, Dale R. Relations with industry., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - College of Engineering., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Berth, Donald F.; Corson, Dale R.
  - Electrical Engineering., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Personius, Catherine J.
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Canoyer, Helen G. Admissions.
  - New York State college of Home Economics., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Admissions.
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Canoyer, Helen G.; Loberg, Harry J. Admissions.
  - New York State Veterinary College., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Poppensiek, George C. Ford Foundation.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Rogosin, Israel.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Du Vigneaud, Vincent; Luckey, E. Hugh; Deitrick, John E.; Trask, Frederick K.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Fuchs, Fritz F.; Trask, Frederick K.; Hinsey, Joseph C.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Deitrick, John E.; Case, Everett Needham.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Hinsey, Joseph C.; Trask, Frederick K.
  - Cornell Medical Center - New York Hospital, Minutes of the Executive Faculty., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Medical Center, Minutes of the Executive Faculty., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Medical Center, Minutes of the Executive Faculty., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Medical Center, Finances., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Medical Center - New York Hospital, Joint Administrative Board., 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Medical Center -New York Hospital, Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Rockefeller, William; Vanderwarker, Richard D.
  - Cornell Medical Center - New York Hospital, Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research. Rockefeller, William; Vanderwarker, Richard D., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Law School. Forrester, Ray; Linowitz, Sol M.; Warren, Earl; Curtiss, W. David; Maresi, P.H.; Franck, Thomas M.; Ritchie, John; Kerr, Clark; Muskie, Edmund S. Law School Fund; Cornell Legal Aid Clinic; Hughes Hall Dedication; Inspection report., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder S)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Moore, David G.; Risley, Robert F.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Carbery, Muriel R.
  - Malott Hall Dedication., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Malott, Deane W.; Malott, Robert H.; Case, Everett Needham; Sloan, Alfred P.
  - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Carmichael, William D.; Summer skill, John. Ford Foundation; American Council on Education; Sloan Institute of Hospital Administration at Cornell University; Accreditation.
  - School of Hotel Administration., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - School of Hotel Administration., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Venu Gopaul, Myral. Hotel Ezra Cornell; IBM; Data processing.
  - School of Education., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - School of Education., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Stutz, Frederick H.; Bruce, Mathew H.
  - School of Education., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Stutz, Frederick H. Cornell University Educational Placement Bureau.
  - School of Education., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Graduate School of Nutrition., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Barnes, Richard H.; Donlon, Mary H.
  - Graduate School., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Donlon, Mary H.; Cooke, W. Donald; Boynton, Damon.
  - Fellowships., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Malott, Deane W. Malott Fellowship; Owens-Corning Corporation; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; Ford Foundation; Esso Corporation.
  - Unclassified Students., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Military Science and Tactics - ROTC., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Miller, Josiah B.
  - Air ROTC., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    Sullivan, Richard D.
  - Physical Education and Athletics., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Kane, Robert J.; Harp, Tom; Todd, Walter L.; Mackesey, Thomas W. National Collegiate Athletic Association; American Athletic Union; Recruiting.
  - Physical Education and Athletics., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Kane, Robert J. Lynah Rink; Nutri-Bio controversy; Tar Young Ski Area.
  - Ivy League. Kane, Robert J.; Harnwell, Gaylord P. National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Ivy League., 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Kane, Robert J.; Harnwell, Gaylord P.; Marcham, Frederick G. Schedules.
  - Naval ROTC., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Matters Relating to All ROTC., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Keese, William B.; Marcham, John; Javits, Jacob K.; Sullivan, Richard D.; Deuterman, Harold T.
  - Newman Laboratory., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Wilson, Robert R.; Hoyle, Fred. Synchrotron.
  - Newman Laboratory., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Gold, Thomas.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory Minutes., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Ross, Ira G.
  - Summer Session., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Smith, W.A.
  - Social Science Research Center., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Thompson, Wayne E.
  - Cornell Plantations., 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Wright, Theodore P.
  - Infirmary and Clinic., 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    Todd, Walter L. Gannett Clinic; Gannett Foundation.
  - Cornell United Religious Work (CURW)., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    Tormey, Richard; Jaquith, L. Paul; Konvitz, Milton R. Cornell in Central America Project.
  - Danforth Foundation., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Rankin, Robert.
  - Alumni Office., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Bradley, Hunt; Gittins, Thomas William.
  - Cornell Clubs., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Bradley, Hunt; Carry, Patricia J.; Stevenson, Adlai E. Cornell Art Tour.
  - Alumni News., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    Hoag, W.G.; Neild, Walter K.
  - Scholarships, Grants, Gifts., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Purcell, Robert W.; Schurman, George M.; Loveland, Chester H. Purcell Scholarship Fund; James Foundation; Old Dominion Foundation.
  - Scholarships, Grants, Gifts., 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Malott, Deane W. IBM; Shell Companies Foundation; GLF.
  - Prizes., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Messenger Lectures., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    De Romilly, Jacqueline; Chastel, Andre; Demorest, Jean-Jacques; Sartre, Jean-Paul; Eliot, T.S.; Feynman, Richard P.
  - Dog Laboratory, Veterinary Virus Research Institute., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SUNY., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Gould, Samuel B.; Moore, Frank C.; Murray, J. Lawrence; Corson, Dale R.; Alien, James E. Division of Biological Sciences.
  - SUNY., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Fretwell, Elbert K.; Moore, Frank C.; Kurd, T. Norman.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Kuusisto, Allan A.; Alien, James E.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Kuusisto, Allan A.; Kille, Frank R.; Fretwell, Elbert K.; Alien, James E.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Fretwell, Elbert K.; Alien, James E.; Nyquist, Ewald B.
  - Degrees., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Regents., 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Srb, Adrian M. Division of Biological Sciences; Albert Einstein Chair in Science.
  - Key to President's File., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - A Miscellaneous., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Adelmann, Howard B. Arecibo; Agency for International Development.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Alexander, Robert E.; Altschul, Frank; Aly, Bower.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Ashby, Eric; Antell, B.W.; Knight, Douglas M. Association of American Medical Colleges; Centennial Convocation.
  - A Miscellaneous., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Zwingle, J.L.; Atwood, Sanford S. Avalon Foundation; Association of Graduate Schools.
  - American Miscellaneous., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Morrow, Glenn R.; Bronfenbrenner, Urie. American Association of University Professors; American Institute of Indian Studies; American Men of Science; Academic freedom.
  - American Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 17-20)
    Johnston, Elton L.; Thackrey, Russell I.; Ostar, Allan W.
  - American Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges Annual Convention., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Thackrey, Russell I.
  - American Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges Annual Meeting., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - American Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges Annual Meeting., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - American Council on Education., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Cox, Lanier; Wilson, Logan. Internships.
  - Applications for Jobs., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Intercollege Committee on Archaeology., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - University Committee on the Arts., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Kelly, Burnham; Guerlac, Henry; McConkey, James R.
  - Association of American Colleges., 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Davidson, Carter. National Defense Education Act.
  - Association of American Universities., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    McCurdy, Charles P. National Humanities Foundation.
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Ingalls, Lester W.
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Black, Max. Humanities Council.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Boyd, Julian P.; Bolman, Frederick DeW.; Brady, Nyle C.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Freeman, Orville L.; Bronfenbrenner, Urie; Brady, Nyle C.; Brooks, Francis J.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Brooke, Francis J.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Buszek, Beatrice R.
  - Division of Biological Sciences., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Morison, Robert S.; Corson, Dale R.; Palm, Charles E.
  - Division of Biological Sciences., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Morison, Robert S.; Corson, Dale R.
  - Division of Biological Sciences., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Palm, Charles E.
  - Division of Biological Sciences., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Palm, Charles E.; Morison, Robert S.
  - Biology Letter, Division of Biological Sciences., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Palm, Charles E.; Federer, W.T.; Wimsatt, William A.; Corson, Dale R.
  - Biology Letter, Division of Biological Sciences., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Corson, Dale R.; Wimsatt, William A.; Palm, Charles E.
  - Biology Letter, Division of Biological Sciences., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Corson, Dale R.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Reichmann, Felix; McManus, John F.; Loosley, Robert O. Centennial Celebration; Centennial exhibition; Centennial awards; Centennial campaign.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Reichmann, Felix; Heckscher, August. Centennial Celebration.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Case, Everett Needham. Centennial Celebration.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Loosley, Robert O. Centennial Celebration; Centennial film.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Centennial Celebration; Centennial campaign.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Noyes, Jansen; Healey, George H. Centennial campaign.
  - Centennial., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Centennial film.
  - Centennial Planning Committee., 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder S)
    Healey, George H.; Mackesey, Thomas W. Centennial Celebration.
  - Centennial Celebration Committee., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Kidera, Robert A.; Comstock, Richard H. Lincoln Center Week; Centennial Convocation.
  - Centennial Celebration Committee., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Healey, George H.; Eager, George B.; Comstock, Richard H.; Abrams, Morris H. Centennial Celebration; Centennial campaign; "Cornell at Lincoln Center."
  - Centennial Celebration Committee. Healey, George H. Cornell Collegium., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Loosley, Robert 0.; Noyes, Jansen; Kidera, Robert A.; Meyer, Loren.
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Noyes, Jansen.
  - Centennial Campaign. Noyes, Jansen., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Centennial Campaign. Noyes, Jansen. Lincoln Center Week., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Noyes, Jansen; Loosley, Robert O. Centennial Celebration.
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Kac, Mark; Black, Max.
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Noyes, Jansen; Einaudi, Mario; Loosley, Robert 0. Cornell Collegium.
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Noyes, Jansen. International Student Conference.
  - Centennial Campaign., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Clark, Van Alan; Reichmann, Felix; Noyes, Jansen. Centennial Convocation.
  - Airplane Account Sheets., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
  - Airplane Manifests and TAs., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Airplane., 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Airplane Correspondence., 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Airplane Operation., 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Aircraft., 1953-1960 (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
  - Airplane., 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
  - Airplane Receipts., 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 33-34)
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Catherwood, Martin P.; Clark, Van Alan.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Conant, James B.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Cook, Philip C.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Research Park Advisory Committee., 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Burton, John E.; Park, Roy H.
  - Carnegie Corporation., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Gardner, John W.; Mahoney, Margaret E. Carnegie Corporation of New York; United States Agency for International Development; Cornell Latin American Year; Center for International Studies.
  - Carpenter, Walter S., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Sloan, Alfred P. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; Carpenter Professorship.
  - Condolences., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Conferences., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Congratulations and Acknowledgements., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Lee, Clarence H.
  - Conferences., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Bills and New York State Bills. Nelson, Gaylord; Javits, Jacob K.; Keating, Kenneth B., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Latin American Year., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    MacLeish, William H.; Keast, William R. Carnegie Corporation.
  - Cornell Latin American Year., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    MacLeish, William H.; Humphrey, Hubert H.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    David, Herbert H.; Dean, William Tucker; Dalby, Norma R.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Demorest, Jean- Jacques; Dorf, Philip; Dowd, Douglas F.; Dominguez, Martin E.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Detweiler, John G.
  - E Miscellaneous. Eastman, Edward R.; Eastwick, Joseph L.; Clark, John M. East-West Center, University of Hawaii., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - E Miscellaneous. Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Eliot, T.S.; Eastwick, Joseph L.; Einaudi, Mario., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - E Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Esso Education Foundation.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Sammartino, Peter.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Fisher, Ruth G.; Fitzpatrick, Edwin J.; Fleishmann, Barbara J.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Retirement Housing., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Malott, Deane W.
  - Ford Foundation., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Hill, Forest F.; Brewster, Kingman; Bowles, Frank; Heald, Henry T. Six Year Ph.D. Program; Centennial Campaign.
  - Ford Foundation., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Heald, Henry T.
  - Ford Foundation., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Bowles, Frank; Heald, Henry T.; Hill, Forest F.; Heussler, Robert; Armsey, James W. Six Year Ph.D. Program.
  - 6 Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Gilchrist, James M. Given Foundation.
  - 6 Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Goldberg, Arthur Abba; Gordis, Elizabeth R.; Gold, Thomas; Goheen, Robert F.
  - 6 Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Grasselli, Caesar A.; Guerlac, Henry; Grohmann, H. Victor. Guggenheim Aviation Safety Center at Cornell; John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation; Daniel and Florence Guggenheim Foundation.
  - Geneva Experiment Station., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Barton, Donald W.
  - H-HN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Holland, Jerome H.; Harriman, W. Averell; Hacker, Andrew; Haloua, Gaston D.
  - H-HN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Havemann, Ernest; Heckscher, August.
  - H-HN Miscellaneous., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Henning, Dyle G.; Hinchcliff, Emerson; Hewitt, George F. Trojan Horse.